<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Victor Sports Odds</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <!--    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>-->


    <string name="title1_con">Every online operator wants to beat their competitors, and Victor Sports Odds achieves so by providing some of the best football odds.
        BetVictor is able to squeeze an extra point or two out of some of its top football bets by taking lower margins, which seasoned punters will not only notice, but enjoy.
        On the other hand, newcomers and casual fans can cash out on accumulators early, but our favorite parts of the site are the bet calculator and results service.</string>

    <string name="title2_con">Taking advantage of Victor Sports Odds best odds guaranteed is one of the finest methods to stretch the odds.
        Place your wager early in the day, after 9 a.m., and if the price rises, you can profit or remain with your early price.
    BetVictor has gone above and beyond for their customers by introducing a "Lengthen The Odds" offering for all of their horse racing markets.
        This is a great method to wager, and you may obtain ridiculous odds on your favorite runner winning by a large margin.</string>

    <string name="title3_con">Victor Sports Odds has previously won honors for their pricing system. Their current structure is on par with, if not better than,
        the majority of the competition. We were most impressed by their consistency, and they were able to offer fantastic discounts on so many different sports and marketplaces.
    What exactly is BetVictors Best Odds Guaranteed? Victor offers Best Odds Guaranteed,
        which implies that you will be awarded a greater price on horse racing if you select an early price but the beginning price is higher.</string>

    <string name="title4_con">Victor Sports Odds offers a dizzying array of sports. Football dominates the web, and few can compete in terms of market and even game coverage. Aside from that, horse racing is another activity that is brilliantly covered, as are tennis, cricket, golf, rugby, and a variety of US-based sports. But it is not only the variety of sports. The number of markets available on events rivals that of any other bookmaker. When you include the #PriceItUp tool, that number skyrockets. We will talk about it further afterwards.</string>

    <string name="title5_con">After waxing poetic about the design, we will get into the meat of BetVictor.
   The first place to begin is with the in-play betting section. This section of the bookmaker has benefited from the recent revamp and now feels much more connected to
        the rest of the site.
    The best betting tactics for winning every time are matched betting and arbitrage betting. They both cover every market outcome with a profit guarantee. Other strategies, like as value betting, can yield higher long-term returns. They are both covering every market outcome with a guaranteed profit. Other tactics,
        such as value betting, can provide greater long-term rewards.</string>

    <string name="title6_con">Football showcases the entire skill set, and you may select from nearly all of the games available in the football betting department.
        The all-new match centre at the top of the page is fantastic, and the graphics that go with it are second to none. We had want it to be a bit more realistic at times,
        since it does seem to go dead for a while, however this rarely happens if we were being honest.
    BetVictor allows new users to take advantage of its sign-up offer in a variety of ways, but the bonus monies must be spent in accordance with the company terms and conditions.
BetVictor is well-known for its new customer offer, but the online bookmaker also offers a variety of promotions to both new and current customers.</string>

    <string name="title7_con">For us, customer service is among the best in the industry.
        It is worth noting that there are numerous ways to reach them. On-site live chat is accessible, as well as email and phone support.
        BetVictor has a strong presence on Facebook and Twitter, indicating that social media is a possibility.
        Customer care is the assistance you give to your customers both before and after they buy and use your goods or services,
        helping them to have  a simple and pleasurable experience with you.
    </string>

    <string name="title8_con">Victor takes responsible gaming extremely seriously. They were among the first to sign up for the Gamstop initiative, which asks users to prove their identity before depositing and betting on the site. They also contain a variety of features, such as betting restrictions, limited time on site, self-exclusion, and a gambling overview to show how much money players are spending. They also collaborate with a number of organizations that assist those in need, such as Gamcare, Gamblers Anonymous, Gambling Therapy Apps, and Money Advice Service.</string>

    <string name="g1">What is the Victor welcome bonus?</string>
    <string name="g1c">The Victor sign-up offer is simple to redeem, and we will go over how the promotion works, how to redeem the sign-up offer, and how the Victor free bet works.</string>
    <string name="g2">How to Make Use of Victor Free Bets</string>
    <string name="g2c1">Victor allows new users to take advantage of its sign-up offer in a variety of ways, but the bonus monies must be spent in accordance with the company terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="g2c2">You can spend your free bets on any single sports bet as long as the odds are 2.0 or higher. There are no wagering requirements, but your Victor free bets must be used within seven days after being approved.</string>
    <string name="g2c3">Football, horse racing, boxing, tennis, cricket, and rugby union are among the many sports available for wagering at Victor. To utilize your BetVictor free bets, you must first click Use Bonus Funds on your betting slip.</string>
    <string name="g3">How to Get Your BetVictor Free Bets Back</string>
    <string name="g3c">You cannot withdraw the Victor sign-up bonus immediately after earning it. When you use the free bets, any winning bets are paid out in cash and are available for withdrawal as the bet is completed. Any gains will not include your stake.</string>
    <string name="g4">All Victor promos and offers</string>
    <string name="g4c1">Regardless of whether they register other accounts with Victor, Parimatch, or any other brand that we operate, each customer is only eligible for one welcome offer throughout our sports and casino offers.</string>
    <string name="g4c2">Customers can withdraw their real cash balance at any time without impacting their eligibility, award, prize, or wagering for this campaign.</string>
    <string name="g4c3">If a customers account is blocked from placing sports bets, they can still satisfy any wagering requirements or utilise any outstanding bonus monies provided as part of this campaign by contacting customer support.</string>
    <string name="g4c4">If we suspect a customer has abused or is attempting to exploit this offer, we retain the right to revoke "Bonus Funds." Low-risk betting, such as betting on red/black, evens/odds, 1-18/19-36, or covering more than 20 numbers on a single spin (including straight up, splits, streets, corners, baskets, six-lines, dozens, columns, red/black, evens/odds, 1-18/19-36, and section/neighbor bets), will result in the bonus and any winnings being forfeited.</string>
    <string name="g4c5">The Promoter reserves the right to declare the promotion null and void, suspend, cancel, or amend it as a result of an exceptional event or circumstances beyond the Promoter reasonable control, such as the cancellation of a sports event that was a prerequisite for participation or a prize condition. If participation has already occurred, the Promoter may swap the incentive with something of equal or better value. For example, if the event on which the free bet was supposed to be used is canceled, the free bet will be valid on any sports event.</string>

    <string name="tip1">Boxing odds are available before of the matches at Victor Sports Odds. Follow the prices for notable fighters like Tyson Fury and Anthony Joshua,
        as well as any major televised fight, to see who has the highest chance of winning.Most fights will have basic betting markets like Winner, Method of Victory, and Round Betting. Obviously, the larger the battle, the more markets will be available.
        A match like the last heavyweight clash between Tyson Fury and Deontay Wilder could have had dozens of markets.</string>
    <string name="tip2">Football tips, odds comparison, match previews, data, and the latest market changes on all things football are all available at Victor Sports Odds.
        We strive to comb through football betting odds in order to provide you, the user, with a unique experience that highlights the finest value plays.
        Choosing the best of today football bets and odds for rapid access to place your bet, check the data, or read our match previews.
    This page has all of the finest odds for the Premier League, Champions and Europa Leagues, EFL, FA Cup, and League Cup, which are updated daily to bring
        you the most competitive rates available from a variety of bookies.</string>
    <string name="tip3">Victor Sports Odds offers UFC odds on the major fights before of the fights. Follow the prices for big fighters like Khabib Nurmagomedov and Conor McGregor, as well as any major televised fight, to see who has the highest probability of winning.
The Ultimate Fighting Championship (UFC) is a mixed martial arts promotional organization based in Las Vegas, Nevada. It is by far the largest MMA organization in the world, with the majority of the sports top competitors signed solely to their roster. Dana White, the UFC current President,
    has been in control since 2001 and has transformed the organization into a multibillion-dollar enterprise.</string>
    <string name="tip4">The current snooker odds for both outrights and match betting for the largest televised tournaments are available at Victor Sports Odd.
        We emphasize the players chances using our unique likelihood percentage.
Snooker betting is most commonly done online via bookmaker websites/apps, but if you prefer a more conventional method,
        you may also place a snooker bet in-store at your local betting shop. Snooker betting is quite popular,
        especially with the development of in-play betting. With markets like game betting and highest break, as well as the structure of the sport,
        it is truly set up to be a terrific sport to bet on.</string>
    <string name="tip5">Victor Sports Odds compares the odds for every horse racing in the United Kingdom and Ireland.
        We provide you the percentage probability each horse has of winning the race using our proprietary Probability Percentage factor.
Best Odds Guaranteed means that if you support a horse at a given price with a bookmaker,
        if the odds for that horse rise after you place your bet and it wins, the bookmaker will
        pay you out at the highest priced odds. For example, if a punter backs a horse to win a race at odds of 4/1,
        but the price climbs to 9/2 when the race begins and the bet wins,
        the bookmaker will pay out at 9/2 odds if they provide Best Odds Guaranteed.</string>
    <string name="tip6">Golf is one of the most popular sports to bet on, and at Victor Sports Odd,
        we offer golf odds and advice for both major circuits weekly tournaments.
        We will show you exactly how likely the selection is to win using our proprietary odds grids.
Golf betting can be done in a variety of ways.
        Golf bets can be placed in-store and over the counter at high-street bookmakers,
        or online via bookmaker websites and mobile apps. Bet on a wide range of golfing markets,
        from the overall winner of an individual tournament to who you believe will win a given round, and many, many more.</string>
    <string name="tip7">The current cricket odds for matches or outrights, both domestically and internationally, are available at BetVictor Sports Odd.
        We simplify our odds grids with our unique probability percentage so you can see what percentage chance the teams have of winning.
Our team of specialists will provide the best cricket betting tips for major tournaments both worldwide and domestically.
        Cricket is genuinely an all-year sport, with a plethora of outright betting markets available,
        as well as a plethora of in-play betting odds for nearly every match.</string>
    <string name="tip8">Victor Sports Odds compares the most recent match betting and outright darts odds for all major tournaments. Our one-of-a-kind grids show the percentage chance that each pick has of winning.
You can wager on darts online using bookmaker websites/apps, or you can visit your local high-street bookmaker and place a physical bet over the counter. Darts has grown in popularity as a betting sport since it allows bettors to take advantage of bookies live in-play markets and a variety of darts odds.
A money line bet is one of the most common and straightforward darts wagers, in which you identify the matches outright winner.</string>

    <string name="way_tit1">What methods of triumph are there to bet on?</string>
    <string name="way_tit1c">In boxing, there are a few ways to win a fight, and the majority of these are covered in the Method of Victory market. KO (knockout)/TKO (technical knockout)/DSQ (Disqualification), Decision/Technical Decision, and Draw/Technical Draw are the most common possibilities.</string>
    <string name="way_tit1c2">KO: The most spectacular boxing finish. When one boxer knocks out another, the injured fighter is unable to continue or beat the 10 count</string>
    <string name="way_tit1c3">TKO: A technical knock out occurs when a referee believes a boxer is unable to continue the bout safely and declares the fight over. The fighter may still be standing, but they are unable to defend themselves. When a fighter is badly injured by a cut and is deemed unable to continue by the doctor/referee, it is also considered a TKO.</string>
    <string name="way_tit1c4">Disqualification: The fight may be ended by disqualification. If one competitor persistently and fragrantly violates the rules of the sport, the referee may interrupt the fight and award the victory to the other fighter. Biting, headbutting, or hitting low/on the back of the head are all examples of rules violations.</string>
    <string name="way_tit1c5">A decision victory occurs when the battle comes to an end and either the referee (in small fights) or three independent judges (in important fights) decide who has won. They normally use a ten-point system, with the best fighter in each round receiving 10 points and the other combatant receiving 9 points. Knockdowns/completely won rounds are deducted points, as are infringements like as low blows.
        A points triumph is another term for it. E.g. On points, Anthony Joshua.</string>

    <string name="way_tit2">What happens if my Anytime Scorer bet option does not appear in the game?</string>
    <string name="way_titc1">If your player does not participate in the game, the online bookmaker will cancel your wager and refund your money. Your bet will be a loser if your player comes on as a substitution and does not score, just as it would be a loser if your player is substituted and does not score.
        While we strive to have our anytime scorer tip up as soon as possible before a match, you may be better off waiting until team news to see if our selection is playing or not.</string>

    <string name="way_titc2">We are happy to be the home of the Probability Percentage rating, which is applied to all odds on the site at BetVictor Sports Odds.
    This rating provides you the exact % probability that option has of winning, simplifying how we present the odds and giving you a better grasp of what they actually are mean.
    We also provide the odds in Fractional or Decimal form.</string>

    <string name="way_tit3">What is the distinction between UFC and MMA?</string>
    <string name="way_tit3c1">The promotional company brand name is UFC. The sport of mixed martial arts is known colloquially as MMA. Bellator, ACA (Absolute Championship Akhmat), FNG (Fight Nights Global), and Cage Warriors are some other MMA promotions.
Basic UFC betting normally comprises the Winner market (choose the winner of the fight) and Total Rounds (generally pick over or under 1.5/2.5/3.5/4.5 rounds) as well as the Method of Victory market (will the fight result in a decision, submission, or KO/TKO).
Individual bout prop bets include the fight going the distance and the Method of Victory market (will the fight result in a decision, a submission, or a KO/TKO).</string>

    <string name="way_tit4">How do you place a snooker bet?</string>
    <string name="way_tit4c1">This type of betting is only for a given frame. Betting on different frames of the game is a highly fascinating betting strategy. For example, you might wager on a player to win one frame and then lose the next three.
Anything can happen, and you can gamble on that part of the game in particular, frame by frame. Punters, or bettors, frequently have an understanding of such matters. They could wager that a player will lose the first three games and then win the next three.
Given the unpredictability of this sport, where a player can come back from a large disadvantage, betting frame by frame makes the game more intriguing to watch</string>

    <string name="way_tit5">Horse Racing Predictions</string>
    <string name="way_tit5c1">Bookmaker websites and apps are likely to be the earliest to display horse race results since they want to settle bets as soon as possible. When looking for the winners and losers of a certain horse race, it is best to start with those. The team is also very efficient when it comes to displaying quick horse racing results.
Not all horse races are accessible for streaming, but many are, and most bookmakers enable their customers to view live horse racing through their websites/apps. In most situations, the punter must put a bet on the race with that bookmaker in order to watch the event, while other bookies do not require this.</string>

    <string name="way_tit6">Odds on Golf Betting</string>
    <string name="way_tit6c1">Golf betting can be done in a variety of ways. Golf bets can be placed in-store and over the counter at high-street bookmakers, or online via bookmaker websites and mobile apps. Bet on a wide range of golfing markets, from the overall winner of an individual tournament to who you believe will win a given round, and many, many more.
The PGA Tour is the place to be for both players and betting activity! With larger fields and more recognizable players, the PGA Tour is more popular with golf bettors. BettingOdds.com publishes weekly betting previews with the most recent PGA Tour odds and tips.</string>

    <string name="way_tit7">Cricket Odds and Betting</string>
    <string name="way_tit7c1">The World Cup is, like any other sport, the peak of cricket and provides punters with the option to put a variety of bets in the hopes of making a substantial profit. There are World Cups in both limited overs and 50 overs cricket, as well as T20 cricket.
</string>
    <string name="way_tit7c2">The Ashes, which is fought every other year between England and Australia, is an engrossing clash between two world-class cricket teams and a terrific competition to bet on with many cricket odds.</string>
    <string name="way_tit7c3">T20 Club/Franchise cricket is also a popular bet because it is a much faster-paced game with plenty of runs and boundary shots. There are numerous franchise contests all around the world, including the Indian Premier League (IPL), Big Bash, Pakistan Super League (PSL), and our own Vitality Blast.</string>
    <string name="way_tit7c4">The Hundred is a new format introduced last year by the England Cricket Board. It is even shorter than T20 cricket, with matches consisting of a hundred balls played in 10 x 10 ball sets. It was incredibly popular last summer and should provide an excellent betting chance in the future.</string>

    <string name="way_tit8">How does a darts match work?</string>
    <string name="way_tit8c1">To score points in most professional darts matches, two players take turns throwing three darts at a dartboard.
The dartboard is divided into 20 radial portions that signify points ranging from one to twenty, as well as two rings that double or triple the points scored if the dart lands in them. The bullseye is in the center of the dartboard, with the inner bullseye worth 50 points and the outer bullseye earning 25.
The 501 scoring system is used in the great majority of professional darts tournaments. Players battle against one another to reduce their score from 501 to zero, typically finishing on a double. The first player to accomplish so wins the leg at stake.</string>

    <string name="about">Victor mobile offers a similar dynamic to the desktop interface, but with one slick difference: you swipe. Rather than seeing everything on a single page, the three elements are separated by a few swipes. When you launch the iOS or Android app, you will see the most recent upcoming events. Swipe left to access the sports menu, and right to view your bet slip.</string>
    <string name="about2">In terms of structure, Victor adheres to the normal left-to-right search dynamic. What exactly do we mean by this? On the left side of the page, you will notice a vertical list of sports betting possibilities. After starting here, you will be sent to the center of the page, where you will see a grid containing fixtures and odds. Finally, after selecting your selection, you proceed to the betting slip on the right-hand side of the website.
        This strategy has proven to be efficient for the better part of a decade, and this holds true at Victor Sports Odds.</string>


    <string name="back_button">back_button</string>
    <string name="back_ground">back_ground</string>
    <string name="tab_bar">tab_bar</string>
    <string name="image_button">image_button</string>
    <string name="close_button">close_button</string>
    <string name="logo_image">logo_image</string>
    <string name="click_to_nextpage">click_to_nextpage</string>

</resources>